servicebench.com 2006-12-12

# ServiceBench, Inc.

### Privacy Policy

ServiceBench is committed to maintaining the privacy of your information and to safeguard your privacy on line.  Please read the information below to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make use of the services offered by ServiceBench.   

**1.   _What information is gathered/tracked_  **

ServiceBench only collects information that you, a Web site user, provide directly to ServiceBench.  Except for ServiceBench Users (as defined below), we do not use cookies to store or track information about you. 

ServiceBench will maintain this information about you in strict confidence, will take commercially reasonable measures to protect this information against illegal or unauthorized access, and will not release it to any person unless authorized by you or compelled by court order or other legal process.  

This privacy policy does not apply to ServiceBench clients or their business partners who log into ServiceBench’s proprietary applications through this Web site (“ServiceBench Users”). We do use cookies to store and track information about ServiceBench Users. If you are a ServiceBench User and register with ServiceBench and obtain a ServiceBench ID, user ID and password, personal information is obtained (name, email address, ServiceBench Client with whom you are affiliated, etc.).  This information is used to personalize/tailor the site to meet your specific needs and/or provide you with additional services pursuant to a separate agreement. 

**2.   _How do we use this information_**  

We internally use the information as an on-going effort to improve our content to better serve your needs and to market our products and services to you. 

We may use this information to provide demographic and usage information to our business partners.  We would aggregate information about you with information about other users and may release this aggregated information so long as you and the other users are not identified. 

**3.   _With whom does ServiceBench share the information_**  

As a general rule, ServiceBench does not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission.  If you are a business partner of a ServiceBench Client and are using this Web site as authorized by such ServiceBench Client, you authorize ServiceBench to disclose the information you provide about yourself with such ServiceBench Client as necessary in connection with the performance of ServiceBench services. 

**4.   _Privacy Policy Changes_**  

If we decide to make changes to our privacy policy, we will post the changes in this document, which will always be available to you on this Web site.  Changes to this policy will be effective when posted to the Web site.  Please feel free to review this document periodically for any changes.
